->problem
    Create a stone paper scissors game
    Rules - stone beats scissors, scissors beat paper, paper beats stone.

->Plan 
    1.when user provides an input, provide a randomized input from computer
    2.compare both inputs, the one with higher input wins
    3.Ask if wants to play again, if yes, repeat, if no exit

->subproblems division
   1. an array to store three inputs
   2. make computer generate one value using random
   3. take user input
   4. compare both, and provide one output for winner.
